moviescapital.com 2010-12-03

# Online Movies - Download Full Movies & Watch movies Online

We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and security.

**Privacy Statement for MoviesCapital.com**

Moviescapital has created this privacy statement to describe our firm and honest commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: "MoviesCapital.com" 

. We seek to protect your private information so that you have a pleasurable and safe viewing experience on our Web site. We will not sell, rent, trade, or disclose your personally identifiable information to anyone or any 3rd party except as explained in this policy. Please return to this page from time to time, as we will be updating this statement as our services continue to grow. We welcome and encourage questions, comments, and suggestions. Please contact us at [Moviescapital@yahoo.com](mailto:Moviescapital@yahoo.com) with any questions or concerns.

**Personally Identifiable Information**

What Personally Identifiable Information Is:

Personally identifiable information is your name, country and e-mail address. In order to protect our customers we collect the minimum information needed for customer tracking and nothing more.

**Where We Collect Personally Identifiable Information**[ Moviescapital.com](http://www.singahe.com/) collects personally identifiable information when you (1) subscribe to the moviescapital.com website, (2) enter contests, (3) login to the website (walso monitor IP addresses to prevent abuse of our system and to detect any fraudulent activities)  (4) submit feedback, questions, or "contact us" messages (5) When downloading/streaming movies from moviescapital.com members area (in order to track your membership plan depletion).

**How We Use Personally Identifiable Information**

[ Moviescapital.com](http://www.singahe.com/) uses your personally identifiable information to personalize your experience on our Web site, to deliver products and/or services ordered and/or purchased by you and to contact you.

**Who We Disclose Personally Identifiable Information To**

[ Moviescapital.com](http://www.singahe.com/) will not sell, rent, trade, or disclose your personally identifiable information to anyone except as explained in this policy. You may opt-out of receiving email updates by sending an email with "remove" in the subject line to [moviescapital@yahoo.com](mailto:moviescapital@yahoo.com). It may take up to 10 days to be removed from the list.[Moviescapital.com](http://www.singahe.com/)  may also disclose your personal information to law enforcement personnel, government officials, or others when we, in our sole discretion, believe that disclosure is necessary to prevent violations of the law, injury to person or property, or any harm to [Moviescapital.com](http://www.singahe.com/) or other members of the website.

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Employees are notified in staff meetings of security policies and practices regularly. Access to data limited and employees obtain access to log files by a secured password. Moviescapital.com periodically reviews web security and ensures that all policies and practices are adhered to within the company.

**Correct/Update or Cancel Information**

Users can change their information with Moviescapital.com by editing their account details inside the members area

.   
**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you may contact:
